損さ悲しみを言う!
自分らしさを力に迷いながらでもいい
See  you  guys!
Y  Mono  Daniela
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
Oh,  yeah,  yeah
Let's  see.
Mo -e -e -e -e -e -e!
is  he  human  or  monster  why  do  you  hide  Sasuke
Uchiha  do  I  frighten  you  are  you
shocked  by  my  true  form  why  do  you  run  and  hide
why
Why  do  you  always  run  away?
Come  on!
It's  to  me!
Yeah!
Get  it!
Come  on!
You  can  do  it!
That  was  awesome!
Come  on!
It's  him!
Here.
It's  that  Gaara!
He's  really...
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
Yeah.
Thank  you.
Let's  go.
UUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUU
I  won't  let  you  get  away,  you  can't  escape,  do
you  hear,  Sasuke  Uchiha?
We're  in  it.
Thank  you.
Hold  on!
Why  me?
on  me.
Yes.
Thank  you.
so  lonely
a  minute  here.
Here  we  go.
in  Sasuke's  eyes.
Be  careful.
You  may  not  be  able  to  read  him
as  well  as  you  think.
When  we  finally  fight,  it  won't  be  to  advance  to
the  next...
One
one  standing  will  feel  the  full  value  of  his
existence.
what  you  want,  too.
You  want  to  confirm  the  value  of  your  existence,
don't  you?  To  know  if  you're  truly
Your  existence  is  stronger.  Yours,  or  the  one
facing  you  with  murder  in  his  eyes.
Thank  you.
and  sense  of  pur -
OBJECT  FEAR!
that  of  a  coward!  Come  out  and  fight  me!  Show  me
that  I'm  wrong!  Prove  that  your  existence
YOU 'LL  NEVER  FEEL  IT!
ATTACK!
Thank  you.
Reason.
Shh!
himself  the  guilt
I  NEED  TO  BE  THE  ONE  TO  KILL  HIM!
Thank  you.
Looks  like  it  worked!
I  see!  So  that's  what  it  is!
Amazing!
Ah!
Looking  forward  to  this,  this  pain.
an  opponent  capable  of  wounding  me  so  badly!  Such
a  victory!
No  one  has  ever  wounded  Gaara.
fiber  of  his  body.  For  all  Gata's  strength,  it's
only  his  right  arm  that's  been  transformed.
There's  more.  So  much  more!
What  the  hell  is  this  guy?
How  many  of  these  things  are  going  to  grow  out
of  him?
What?
We  won't  do  it!
This  level
You're  finished!
You
Oh
I
You
BATTLE!
but  costly  using
Don't  sweat  it,  I'm  actually  very  impressed.
empty
more  than  twice.
Well,  for  one  thing,
Not  only  will  it  not  work,  but  the  attempt  can
drain
die.
Even  if  the  worst  doesn't  happen,  nothing  good  can
come  of  it.
Ah
Is  that  it  that  was  the  best  demonstration
Resistance!  That's  just  pathetic,  truly.
You're  far  too  soft  and  forgiving!
There's  a  reason  itachi  let  me  live  a  reason  he
chose  me  to  be  the  one  to  track
I
GRRRRRRRR
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Thank  you.
S .O .S.
Aaaaah!
Set!
I  can't  move  my  body!
Thank  you.
I  don't  know.
Sasuke!
You
Thank  you.
Those  two.
Ha!
Thank  you.
Sensei  said  that  Bruiser
What  do  you  want?
outward  appearance  may  be  different  but  he's  the
one  you  know  as  Gaara  my  father
used  ninjutsu  to  ensure  I  be  the  strongest  of
shinobi  infusing  my  unborn
self  with  a  sand  spirit  and  as  a  result  I
birth  to  me.  I  was  born  a  monster.  So  this  is
what  he  was  talking  about!  He
hey  little  girl  hmm  I  guess  now  would  be  the
time  to  tell  you  I'm
You
Sasuke!
Thank  you.
If  you  let  your  hate
of  that  curse  mark.
happens.
I  have  to  get  this  under  control!
So  it's  you  you're  the  one
Huh
myself  as  long  as
Guys  get  up  we  have  to  go
You
No!
Move  it!
Uggggggggggg
You
Let's  go!
now
I  can't  handle  this  guy!
Now  let  me  feel  alive!
you
Thank  you.
Agarra,  you  can't  do  this!
Tomorrow!
Medical  Corps,  our  leader,  Lord  Kazekage,  has  asked
that  I  see
Yashimaru,  sorry.
The  wound  you  got,  does  it  hurt?
It'll  heal  in  no  time.
when  someone  is  struck  or  cut
it's  a  feeling  that's  very  hard  to  take.
You  don't  feel  normal.
explaining  it  very  well  basically  it's  a  situation
you  want  to  avoid
Thank  you.
You're  not  like  me,  Yashimaru?
Like  the  others?
You
Hmm
Everyone
But  it's  not  so  easy  for  us  to  hate  one  another.
Thanks  a  lot,  Yashimaru.
That  helped.  I  think  I  kind  of  understand  what
pain  is  now.
I  see.
too.  Just  like  everyone  else.  I'm  always  in  pain.
You
Thank  you.
Love.
You've  got  it.
Love  is  the  heart's  desire.
My
death,  wants  more  than  anything  to  protect  you.
Yashimaru...
What  is  it,  Gaara?
Thank  you  for  all  of  your  help.
You're  very  welcome.
After  all,
Okay.
Thank  you.
I
I  have  a  feature.
I  need  some  of  your  medicine.
Ha,  ha,  ha,  ha.
Woof,  woof,  woof,  woof.
Woof,  woof,  woof.
Thank  you.
No  one  wants
why  why  do  I  have  to  be  such  a
Thank  you.
.
Why?
Is  it  always  me?
Thank  you.
Who  are  they?
to  serve  someone
Well,  I  wouldn't...
to  have  you.
Sacrifice.
Your  name  is  the
A  demon  that  loves  you.
No  one's  existence.
gift.
out  of  maternal  affection.
It  was  from  her  undying  rage  at  this
No!
Whoa!
Thank  you.
You  were  never  loved,  Gaara.
Never.
but  now
You
Thank  you.
Oh
Love?
The  sand  ought  to
the  love  of  a  mother.  I  believe  your  mother
grain  of  that  sand.
were  the
kind  of
.
I  love  you,  I  love  you,  I  love  you.
Thank  you.
Love  no  one  else.
Only  for  yourself.
And  now...
without  Mooji  Media  Ltd.'s  express  consent.
What's  the  matter?
Don't  you  care  what  happens  to  your  precious
Let  her  go!
Bye.
You  don't  matter!
It's  time!
Whoa!
Summoning  Jutsu!
What  is  it?  What  do  you  want,  kid?
Well,  whatever  it  is,  I  hope  you  brought  along
some  treats.
Oh,  give  me  a  break!
I'm  really  starting  to  hate  you!
Well,  take  that,  you  big  bigot!
Listen!
I  can't  believe  it!
work  I'm  the  only  one  who  can  save  them  worried
about  the  others
When  I
alone
Thank  you.
And  you  should  hurry!
until  you
SAN  SURIKEN!
Ah!
No!
Thank  you.
I've  seen  that  look  before.
In  myself.
Like  me!
I  remember  how  I  hated  them  because  they  hated  me
and  I  couldn't  understand  why.
I  wondered  why  I  even  existed.
The  fox  spirit  that  killed  Iruka's  parents  and
destroyed  our  village  has  taken  over  your  body.
That's  when  I  found  out
It  wasn't  my  fault,  but  everyone
But  then...
Hey,  how  about  we  take  a  ramen  break,  Naruto?
Yeah!  Great  idea!
right  now!
he  feels  about  me
Ramen  Beans  and
stuff  like  this.
I  made  it  better.
Then  even  though  I  had  this  monster  inside  me
even  though  everyone  else  acted  like  I  didn't
exist
in  a  long  time
I'm  really,  really  happy.
They  made  me  glad  to  be  alive
But  when  I  think  back  on  where  I  was  before
nothing  but  pain  and  darkness  what  would  I  be
like  if  I'd  stayed  there  all  alone
I  don't  know.
That's  why  he  hasn't
NO!
Naruto...
What...
What  the...
And  again!
what  is  this  you  come  at  me  and  that's  all
you've  got  all  that  effort
Pfff!
It  doesn't  matter.
Hey!
I
JOKE!
I'll  call  you  Jiu -Jiu -Jiu!
YESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS
You
That  was  a  nice  move  the  kid  pulled
Am  I  not?
God,  I...
All  of  that  worked?
Packed  at  the  base  of  the
The  impact.  Have  I  underestimated  him?
Naruto,  listen  to  me.
If  it's  the  last  thing  you  do  once  you've  got
her.
It's  all  up  to  you.
Sasuke!
Your  comrades?
He's  absolute.
Thank  you.
You
than  I  am.
I  REALLY  DID!
real  strength  is  if  you  never  fight  for  any
So  is  there.
You
HE'S  RELEASING  A  MASSIVE  AMOUNT  OF  CHAKRA!
HOW  IS  HE  DOING  IT?
Thank  you.
MAKVISHA!
LEAVE  MY  EYES
Sasuke,  why  don't  you  take  it  easy  for  a  while?
You  deserve  it!
I  was  a  Maki!
What  happened?
The  power  sucks.
HADLUCK!
EVERYWHERE!
My  body  hasn't  recovered  yet  have  to  use  the  sand
to  defend
My  bra!
From  Naruto's  handbook!
That...
Kid...
Think  I  will  use  both  legs  for  a  barrage  of  4
,000  kicks!
come  from?
Unbelievable  taking  on  God
Not  to  him!
I'M  GONNA  LOSE  TO  A  GUY!
Oh
He's  finally  emerged.
Thank  you.
Possession.
Let  it  go!
And  all  those  clones!
You're  up.
No,  no,  no,  no.
It's  you  this  is  the  end  for  you
You  really  are  good  at  amusing  me.
Naruto!
BREEZE!
Huh?
Not  you!
ZEEEESH!
It's  only  natural  the  boss  would  want  to  help  out
his  henchmen,  isn't  it?
over  a  couple
OPT!
What  are  you  doing  here,  Gamakichi?
Came  to  hang  out!
Huh?
HUH?!
big  ugly  lung  over  there  was
Oh,  yeah,  and  when  he  did  our  friend  here  came
to  my
you,  Pops,  there's  a  heck  of  a  lot  more  to  this
kid  than  meets  the  eye.
Is  that  right?
Okay,  kid,  you're  hereby  accepting
Sit  tight,  I'll  show  you  what
Thank  you.
I'll  take  him  down,  but  not  before  he's  paid  for
what  he's -
Mr.  Flunky!
No!
Yeah!
Whoa!
Thank  you.
This  guy's  no  joke.
Cut  he  so  heavy,  if  I
Hold  on  a  second!
if  you  can  okay  Sakura  it's  his  little  girlfriend
pop  right  kid  I  have  to  take
him  out  otherwise  Sakura's  as  good  as  dead
interesting  interesting
Asamaki!
This  isn't  good!
He's  really  going  to  do  it!
I  have  to  get  out  of  here!
What  the...
What  the  heck  is  that?
A  spiritualist  medium.
To  thank  you!
of  the  manifest
There's  a...
Evidence  that  the  medium's  been  possessed  by  the
Shikaku
by  shikaku
I'm  no  longer  able  to  sleep
The  Chicago
great  but  as  long  as  the  spiritualist  me
The  only  danger.
Vipassum  Jutsu!
Oh
Thank  you.
I  don't  like  this  at  all,  Chief  Toad.  What's
gonna  happen?
You
I'm  finally  free,  here  I  come!
So  that's  the...
...San  Spirit?
Man,  that  is  one  funky  demon!
Yeah!
Water  style,  liquid  bullets!
Oh,  this  is  nice.  I  didn't  know  it  was  going  to
rain.
What  kind  of  a  battle  is  this  turning  into?
Not  in  that  direction!
Will  you  shut  up?
HELLBODY!
Thank  you.
He's  back,  Chief!  There's  one  more  coming!
I  did  it!